Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.twelve Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents S
  - Sapir, Edward (Box 77)
    - signed "E.S."?, 1931 Dec. 31 and Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1932 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 21
      - enc., work of Yiddish Scien. Inst., 1933 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1933 May 3
    - To Boas, 1933 July 7
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 21
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 20
      - enc. orthographic RX from 6 Americanist linguists, 1934 Aug. 15; 5p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1935 May 6
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1936 June 11
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 13 and Nov. 10
      - see Boas, F., 1936 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 22
      - see FB to Swanton, 1937 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1937
      - see FB open letter, 1937 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1937 May 8
    - To Boas, 1937 May 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 6
    - To Boas, 1937 June 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 13
      - see FB, RX of ES for APS grant, 1937 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 31
      - see FB open letter, replies, re: Spain, 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 10; 5p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1938 May 3
    - To Boas, 1938 June 14
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 15
    - From Brand, Donald D., 1936 Dec. 16
    - From Dyk, Walter, 1937 June 2
    - From Fewkes, J.W., 1920 May 19
    - From Haas, Mary R., 1937 June 9
    - From Kroeber, A.L., 1913 Mar. 18
    - From Li, Fang-Kuei, 1937 Feb. 14
    - From Leland, W.G., 1936 Dec. 18
    - From Leland, W.G., 1937 Apr. 20
    - From Lopatin, I.A., 1930 Jan. 27
    - From Pike, Victoria, 1937 June 8
    - From Ray, V.F., 1937 May 30
    - From Sedat, Wm., 1937 June 22
    - From Siebert, F.T., Jr., 1937 May 25
    - From Sywulka, E.F., 1937 July 14
    - From Taylor, A., 1931 May 28
    - From Throop, A.M., 1918 Aug. 15
    - From Townsend, W.C., 1937 May 27
    - From Wissler, C., 1926 Aug.?
    - From (written on Rau, C.), 1926 Aug. 30
    - To Fewkes, J.W., 1920 Apr. 26
    - To Fewkes, J.W., 1920 May 21
    - To Fewkes, J.W., 1920 May 28
    - To Gifford, E.W., 1930 Dec. 26
    - To Hodge, F.W., 1917 Apr. 19; 3p
    - To Leland, W.G., 1936 Dec. 23; 2p
  - Sapir, Jean (Mrs. Edward) (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 18; 4p
  - Saposnekow, Jacob (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 18
  - Sapper, Karl T. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 21
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 15
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1930 May 6
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1902 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 May 8
    - To Boas, 1909 June 13
    - To Boas, 1911 July 26
    - To Boas, 1920 July 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Feb. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 23
  - Sarasin, F. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 10
  - Saraun [?], Christine (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 25; 2p
  - Sarelle (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 6
  - Sargent, D.A. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1893 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1893 June 30
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 15
    - Sargent
  - Sargent, Homer E. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, [1909?] Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, [May 3?] 1910 May 31
    - From Boas, 1910 June 1
    - From Boas, 1910 July 28
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 4
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 24
    - From Boas, 1911 May 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 May 26
    - From Boas, 1911 June 12
    - From Boas, 1911 June 17
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 13; 3p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 6
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 30; 3p
    - From Boas, 1915 May 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 25; 3p
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 1; 3p
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 June 11
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 7; 4p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 11; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 25
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 4
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 17; 4p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1921 May 18
    - From Boas, 1921 Sep. 8
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1923 May 12
    - From Boas, 1923 May 14
    - From Boas, 1923 May 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 29
    - From Boas, 1924 June 30
    - From Boas, 1924 Sep. 20
    - From Boas, 1925 May 22
    - From Boas, 1925 July 8, 1926 July 27
    - From Boas, 1927 May 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 23
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1928 May 7
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 3
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1931 May 29
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 May 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 May 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 July 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 May 25; 3p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 10
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 5; 5p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 May 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 May 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 June 29, Aug. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 29; 3p
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 June 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 7; 2p
    - enc. HES to Fewkes, J.W., 1923 Apr. 21
    - Salish basketry, 1923 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1923 May 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 July 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 25; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 June 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1926 May 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 21
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1927 June 15
      - enc. HES to Columbia Trustees, 1927 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1928 May 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 12
      - Enc. HES to Columbia Trustees, 1929 Aug. 8
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1931 May 24
      - enc. Kramer, Lucy found end of June '31, 1931 June 11; ?
    - To Columbia U., Treas., 1918 Apr. 24
    - To Columbia U., Sec'y, 1930 Dec. 9
    - To Columbia U., Trustees, 1917 Nov. 19
    - To Columbia U., Trustees, 1927 Oct. 11
    - To Columbia U., Trustees, 1929 Aug. 8
    - To Columbia U., Trustees, 1919 Sep. 1
    - To Fewkes, J.W., 1923 Apr. 21; 2p
    - From Fewkes, J.W., 1923 Feb. 14
    - From Fewkes, J.W., 1923 Apr. 28
    - To Teit, J.A., 1912 Aug. 1; 3p
  - Sargent, J.G. (Box 78)
    - From Guthrie, W.D., 1924 Dec. 7
      - enc. with Guthrie, W.D. to FB, 1925 Jan. 5
    - To Guthrie, W.D., 1924 Dec. 30; 2p
      - enc. with Guthrie, W.D. to F.B., 1925 Jan. 5
  - Sargent, Porter (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 26
    - To Boas, 1938 May 21
    - To Boas, 1941 July 8
      - enc. PS to Bingham, Alf. M., 1941 June 27
  - Sargent, Rena P. (Box 78)
    - To Columbia Univ., 1930 May 1
  - Sargent, W.B. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1911 June 23
  - Sarkar, B.K. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 29
  - Sarton, E.M. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 28; 2p
  - Sarton, George (Box 78)
    - See FB open letter, 1941 July 18
    - See FB to Carlson, A.J., 1941 July 31
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 31
    - see FB open letter, Spain, Replies, 1938 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1940 July 7
  - Saslow, George (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 21
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 25
    - To Boas (see Chase, H.W. and enc. with Cattell, McKeen), 1936 Sep. 22
    - To Boas (see Chase, H.W. and enc. with Cattell, McKeen), 1937 Sep. 30
    - To Boas (see Chase, H.W. and enc. with Cattell, McKeen), 1937 Jan. 24; 4p
    - To Boas (see Chase, H.W. and enc. with Cattell, McKeen), 1937 Mar. 1; 2p
    - To Boas (see Chase, H.W. and enc. with Cattell, McKeen), 1937 Mar. 21
    - To Herskovits, Melville, 1936 July 5; 2p
    - From Voorhis, H.O., 1936 Jan. 28
  - Sattler, Helen (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 5; 3p
  - Sattler, Otto -- (German-American League for Culture) (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 20
    - From Boas, 1939 May 15
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 17; 2p
    - From Lips, J.E., 1939 Dec. 7
  - Sauer, A. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6
  - Sauer, Paul Kurt Sauer (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7
    - To Boas?, 1936 Dec. 31
  - Sauerland, C. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1933 June 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 16 and Nov. 22
      - enc. with Hall, G.F., 1934 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 2
  - Saunders, D.A. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 18
  - Saunders, Marion (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 20
  - Saunders, U.G. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 13
  - Savage (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 15
  - Savell, Isabelle K. (Mrs. Morton S--) (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1937 June 28
    - To Boas, 1937 May 2
      - enc., Eugenics, 1937 June 22
  - Saville, Marshall H. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1903 July 24
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 20
    - From Boas, 1905 July 14
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 1; 4p
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
      - see FB to Gordon, G.B., 1916 May 22
      - see FB to Dixon, R.B., 1916 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1923 May 2
    - From Boas, 1923 May 4
    - From Boas, 1924 May 10
    - From Boas, 1924 June 5
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 27
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1925 June 6
    - From Boas, 1930 June 23
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 June 4
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1923 May 19
    - From Hartmann, C.V., 1919 Nov. 18; 4p
  - Sawders, J.C. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 8
  - Sawtell, Ruth O. (Wallis, Mrs. Wilson) (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1931 May 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 5; 2p
    - See FB, 1931 Nov. 22
    - Tozzer, A.M., 1931 Dec. 31; ?
  - Sawyer, J.C. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 18
  - Sayers, Mentana G. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 24
  - Sayres, Wallace S. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1886 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 27
    - See FB, open letter, Spain, replies, 1918 Jan. 27
  - Scammon, R.E. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1931 June 27
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1931 July 3
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 7
    - From Danforth, C.H., 1931 June 29
  - Scarborough, D. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1921 Aug. 2; 2p
  - Scenario Draft (Box 78)
    See Environmental Influences on Motor Habits of Immigrants
    See Nationality Differences in the Use of Symbolic and Pantomimic Gestures
    See Postural Difference in Native and Assimilated Immigrant Groups
    See Motor Habits in the Lives of Various Nationalities
  - Schaaf, Mrs. Edward (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 3
  - Schaarschmidt, Karl M.W. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1882 Feb. 21
  - Schack, W. (Box 78)
    - see Fohs, F.J., 1929 May 29
  - Schaefer-Simmern, W.H., 1936 June 15 (Box 78)
  - Schaeffer, C.E. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 17; 2p
  - Schaffmey (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14
  - Schandorf, Joseph Adjei (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1936 July 13
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 30; 2p
  - Schapera (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 9
  - Schapiro, J.S. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 24
    - see Wiener, Philip P., 1938 Nov. 30
  - Schapiro, Meyer (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1934 May 2
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1934 June 13
  - Schappes Defense Committee (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 27
  - Scharff, Mrs. A.R. (Box 78)
    - To Razovsky, C., 1938 July 24
    - From Razovsky, C., 1938 Aug. 1
  - Scharfstein, R. (Mrs. Z.) (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1936 June 29
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 9
    - From Lessing, Ada, 1936 June 12
  - Scharmann, H.B. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 31
  - Schauffler, W.G. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 15
  - Schaul, Martin W. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 12
  - Schaxel (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 4
  - Scheerer, Martin (Box 78)
    - see FB open letter, 1937 Feb. 4
  - Scheerer Co. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2
  - Schefold, K. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 12
  - Scheidt, Walter (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 2
    - From Boas, 1928 Sep. 25
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 21
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 14
  - Scheiter, O. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1908 May 24
  - Schelle, Reinhold (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 2p
      - (attached to letter from FB to Zoller, C.), 1923 Feb. 2
  - Scheltema, J.F. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1919 May 24
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 8
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1919 May 22
      - (see address of FB to F. Scheltema), 1919 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 3
  - Schelting, A. von (Box 78)
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
  - Schencke, W. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1925 May 18
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 15; 5p
      enc. Inst. Comparative Research, Human Culture, Oslo - re: series of lectures
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 11; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 29
  - Schenkman, I. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 5
  - Schepotieff, A. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 30; 2p
  - Scheppede, G. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 12
  - Scherer (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1886 May 23
  - Scherer, J.A.B. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 13
  - Scherer, Peter (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 27
  - Scherman, Lucian (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 May 6
    - From Boas ca. 1919-1920, 1919 Dec. 31; p.2
    - From Boas, 1927 June 6
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 July 16
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 June 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1914 May 4
    - To Boas, 1914 May 5
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1937 May 13
    - To Boas, 1937 June 4
  - Schevia, Robert (Box 78)
    - See FB open letter, Spain, Replies, 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 3
  - Schevill, Ferdinand (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 2; 3p
  - Schiedt, R.C. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1920 July 30
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 17
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 18
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 15; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 21
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 9; 3p
  - Schieren, Chas. A. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 24
  - Schiff, Alfred (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 14; 4p
  - Schiff, Jacob H., 1904 Jan. 8 (Box 78)
    - 1904 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1904 May 21
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 4
    - From Boas, 1905 June 3
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1906 June 11
    - From Boas, 1906 June 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 May 17
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1910 June 11
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 21; 4p
    - From Boas, 1911 May 3; 4p
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 7; 4p
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 21
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 29; 3p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 June 12
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 1 and May 2
    - To Boas, 1906 May 20
  - Schiff, J. or M. (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1907 May 2
    - To Boas, 1907 May 20
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1910 June 14
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1911 May 4 and May 11
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 30
    - From Parsons, E.C
      - (FB Sec'y), 1921 Aug. 12; 2p
    - To Laufer, 1911 May 8; 8p
    - To Adams, E.D., 1904 Jan. 25
  - Schiff, Mortimer L.* (Box 78)
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 13
  - Schilling, H.K. (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 22
    - From Kroeber, A.L., 1905 Oct. 31
    - See Kroeber, A.L., 1905 Nov. 1
  - Schinke (Box 78)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 23; 2p
  - Schittenheim, A. (Box 78)
    - Testimonial for Dr. Berkenau, 1921 Feb. 15
  - Schitzsch
    - To Boas, 1907 July 20; 2p